

# **Hivindu Punsith**

## Associate Software engineer

### **Profile**

- M hivindupunsith@gmail.com
- +94 75902679
- 73/A1, Watarappala Rd, Mount Lavina
- Hivindu Punsith

### **Education Background**

- Primary and Secondary School
  D S Senanayake College Colombo-07
  2005-2019
- BSc (Hons) in Information Technology Specializing in Software Engineering
   Sri Lanka Institute of Information
   Technology - Malabe

2020 - Present

### References

- Mr. Lahiru Abeysinghe (Technical Lead)
  Wireapps (Pvt) Ltd
  +94718248639 | lahiru@wireapps.co.uk
- Mr. Jinasiri Abeysuriya (Consultant)
  Solex Group Of Companies
  - +94 77736045| jinasiri@solex.lk

### **About Me**

Energetic and passionate undergraduate working towards a BSc (Hons) in Information Technology specializing in Software Engineering at the Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology. I am aiming to use the knowledge that I have acquired from my internship, and my degree program, as well as self-study, teamwork, and hard work, for the well-being of your organization, and am also willing to learn more from this opportunity.

### **Professional Experience**

Associate Software Engineer - Laravel WAD International (PVT) LTD

2022 - Present

Full Stack Developer Intern Delivergate (PVT) LTD **2021 - 2022** 

Key responsibilities:

- Participated in internal company projects.
- Developed web applications using PHP Laravel, and Angular.
- Angular/Laravel/AWS/SQL

### **Skills**

- Solve complex programmatical scenarios.
- Experience working in an Agile environment, using Scrum methodologies, and the ability to collaborate with a development team.
- Server management, deployment, and configuring web servers. (Apache, MySql)
- Front-end development skills (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

### **Soft Skills**

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- · Multi-tasking

### **Extra Curricular Activities**

- Editor of Commerce Society in D.S. Senanayake College Colombo-7 (2019).
- Member of Leo Club in D.S. Senanayake College Colombo 7 (2019)
- Deputy Head Prefect in 2011–2015 Dhamma School Mount Lavinia (2018–2019)
- Member of the Gold Dragon Karate Association (2011–2015).
- All island and zonal dancing competition winnings (2010–2015):
  Kandiyan Dancer.

### **University Projects**

#### Fitness Hub Web Application

(SLIIT - 3 year 2 semester) (Technologies - React Js, Node JS, Mongo DB)

#### Taprobane HandiCrafft Mobile App

(SLIIT - 3 year 2 semester) (Technologies - Flutter, Node JS, Mongo DB)

### Research Project Management Tool For SLIIT 4th Year Students

(SLIIT - 3 year 1 semester ) (Technologies - React Js, Node JS, MongoDB )

#### Mobile application for online food ordering system

(SLIIT - 2 year 2 semester) (Technologies - JAVA, FireBase)

#### Website for a Higher Education Institute

(SLIIT - 2 year 2 semester - ITP module 2021) (Technologies - MERN Stack )

#### Website for a Pharmacy system

(SLIIT - 2 year 1 semester - OOP module 2021) (Technologies - JAVA Servelets , MySQL )

#### Online food ordering system

( SLIIT - 1 year 2 semster - IWT module 2020) (Technologies - HTML , CSS , PHP , SQL )